RAHUL GANGANI

- Rahul.gangani611994@gmail .com
- (+91)8866553166
- Ahmedabad India

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Presently working as a designer for any commercial & residential project for lightings, generating Lux reports & providing the same for better understanding. Seeks an opportunity in a reputed organization where my resourceful experiences and skills will add value to the organizational operations.

EDUCATION

L.J. POLYTECHNIC AHMEDABAD • 2016

DIPLOMA: CIVIL ENGINEERING

SKILLS

- Positive Approach
- Strong Willpower
- Passion to learn new things
- In-depth knowledge of analyzing the problem
- Skilled for any computer
 Software issue

COMPUTER SKILLS

- MS Office
- AutoCAD
- 3ds Max
- Revit
- SketchUp
- Dialux
- 20/20 Design

WORK HISTORY

PLUS LIGHT TECH LTD, FOCUS LIGHTING & FIXTURE LTD - Lighting Designer

AHMEDABAD, INDIA • 08/2021 - Current

- Designing Lights for Residential or Commercial Projects
- Designing as per Architect or Customer Requirement
- Customized lighting strategies based on specific television, theater and concert requirements.
- Developing Lux Report and 3D Views for better Understanding
- Work with other departments to execute the design, technology, and vendor strategy
- · Review, approve and/or modify designs
- Study, evaluate, and recommend if any re-design is required after Architect or Clients Inputs
- Designing something new & Innovative for Interior Lighting.
- Determined best lighting design and techniques according to location and situation.

SELF EMPLOYED - FREELANCER

AHMEDABAD, INDIA • 11/2020 - 08/2021

- Designing Interior for any Residential or Bungalows Projects
- Designing Kitchen as per Standard Rules & Regulations
- · Coordinating with vendors for further work
- Coordinating with Architect for Exterior Work
- After Handover taking care of Client if any attention is required.

SLEEK KITCHENS BY ASIAN PAINTS - Kitchen Designer AHMEDABAD, INDIA • 08/2018 - 11/2020

- Designing Modular & Civil Kitchen as per Site Condition.
- Anticipating and informing clients of additional features which may be of use to them.
- Giving careful consideration to the placement of water and electrical systems to ensure safety.
- Designed detailed kitchen layouts based on client needs, budgets and available supplies.
- Consulted with clients to determine architectural preference to meet overall design goals.
- · Suggesting appropriate materials and finishes.
- · Advance Planning for coming Week.
- Monitoring Carpenters Team for Gujarat.
- Solving any Issue's during Execution and after Installation.
- Informing clients about appropriate care for their kitchens.

HOTEL HILLOCK PVT. LTD - Interior Designer AHMEDABAD, INDIA • 02/2017 - 08/2018

- Determine the client's goals and requirements for the project.
- Specify materials and furnishings, such as lighting, furniture, wall finishes, flooring, and plumbing fixtures.
- Create a timeline for the interior design project and estimate project costs.
- Drawing Preparation as per any site changes.
- Looking for Site Interior and Execution work.
- Defined space requirements from schematic design to construction phase and installation.

ASWADEEP CONSTRUCTION PVT LTD - Civil Engineer AHMEDABAD, INDIA • 03/2016 - 02/2017

- Looking after site Execution work
- Outline client design objectives

LANGUAGES

English:	BZ	Hindi:	C1
Upper intermediate		Advanced	
Gujarati:	C2		
Proficient			